// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'In Dirty Dancing what is the name of the place Baby and her family spend the summer?',
      a: 'Mountain Lake Hotel',
      b: 'Kellermans Resort',
      c: 'Stone Lodge',
      d: 'Pokenos Lake Rest',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Troop Beverly Hills who plays Phyllis -Shelley Long- husband?',
      a: 'Peter Fonda',
      b: 'Ed O Neill',
      c: 'Craig T Nelson',
      d: 'Tom Serrit',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Addams Famliy Values how does Wednesday Addams say she would kill her future husband?',
      a: 'Electrocution',
      b: 'Thing choke him to death',
      c: 'A Guillotine',
      d: 'Scare him to death',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the original 1961 Parent Trap where at camp to the twins figure out they are sisters?',
      a: 'On a canoeing trip',
      b: 'Snooping in camp records',
      c: 'Solitary confinement',
      d: 'Making the same friendship bracelet',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Space Camp what is the name of NASAs campus droid that launches the kids in to space?',
      a: 'JINX',
      b: 'Wall-E',
      c: 'PROT-On',
      d: 'KITT',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Moonrise Kingdom what is the name of the camp that Sam the Khaki Scout runs away from?',
      a: 'Camp Flint',
      b: 'Camp Invanhoe',
      c: 'Falcon Head',
      d: 'Niagara at the Falls',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Meatballs what is the last prank pulled on Morty?',
      a: 'Tent full of spiders',
      b: 'Morty left on bed raft in lake',
      c: 'Morty tied to a tree',
      d: 'Ink on the eye hole of his binoculars',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Heavyweights what animal is Lars afraid of?',
      a: 'Bear',
      b: 'Bees',
      c: 'Squirrel',
      d: 'Baby Deer',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Dirty Dancing what is Babys real name?',
      a: 'Frances',
      b: 'Carla',
      c: 'Margaret',
      d: 'Bernadette',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Heavyweights what is the password to get in to Tonys - Ben Stiller- cage?',
      a: 'Ding Dong HoHo',
      b: 'Yankee Doodles',
      c: 'Open Sesame',
      d: 'Spaghetti',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};